myphoneshop.com.ph 2014-07-30

# Privacy Policy - myPhoneShop - Philippines

**Privacy Policy**  
myPhoneShop (“Company,” “we,” “our,” “us”) understands that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the myPhoneShop, and any further linked pages, features, content, or application services offered from time to time by Company in connection therewith (collectively, the “Site”), or using any of our services, you recognize and accept the practices and policies stated in this Privacy Policy.

**The Policy:**  
This Privacy Policy covers myPhoneShop ‘s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that the Company gathers when you access myPhoneShop ‘s Website and when you use the Company’s services. This policy does not apply to practices of the companies that myPhoneShop does not own or control, or to individuals that the Company does not employ or manage.

**Private Information does Collected:**  
The data we gather from clients enables us to personalize and improve our services, and allows users to set up an account and profile to make purchases via the Website.

**Personal Information You Provide:**  
We obtain and store information you enter on our Website or provide to us in any way. The types of Personal Information procured may include your name, email address, gender, zip code, country, IP address, browser information, and, if you make a purchase through our Website, your credit card number, credit card security code, expiration date, billing address, and shipping address. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to benefit of many of our special features, and you may not be able to check out with your purchase through the Website. The Personal Information is used for such purposes as allowing you to purchase items, improving the content of the Website, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials and the latest features.  
The website’s contents are not directed specifically to children. Users are required to be at least 18 years old, and any user under 18 is considered an unauthorized user. Furthermore, if we learn that a user is under 13 years of age, it is our right to promptly delete any Personal Information we have acquired about the under aged user.

**Automatic Connection of Personal Information:**

  * We accept and store certain types of information when you interact with our Website or services. Company automatically receives and registers information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, page requested, and any items you purchase. This information may be used to customize content or to connect with you about specials and new features.
  * Usage information, such as numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components may also be used in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of data enable us to figure out how often customers use certain parts of the Website or services so that we can make the Website pleasing to many customers as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of data, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, en masse, use our site. We share this type of statistical information so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and our Website, so that they, too, may deliver an optimal online experience. myPhoneShop never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.
  * The tracking we implemented is based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting) and can collect information such as age, gender, interests and interaction with ads impressions. Using the Ads Settings, visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. myPhoneShop and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to your website and across the Internet
  * E-mail Communications: We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from myPhoneShop and the company uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting, helpful and to improve our over-all service. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, simply indicate your preference by making a modification on your account page, or by using the “Unsubscribe” feature in any email we send to you.

About Cookies:

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to identify your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Company cookies do not collect Personal Information, and does not combine general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name and/or email address is.
  * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as allowing you to approve each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Website’s most attractive features.
  * We may use cookies to gather usage or “clickstream” data about you or others who use your computer. This information allows us to deliver targeted content that we believe will be of most interest to potential customers and/or clients.

**Will myPhoneShop share any of the personal information received?**  
The customers’ Personal Information is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We only share Personal Information as described:

**Affiliated Companies We Do Not Control:**  
myPhoneShop is affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses sell items to you through Company’s Website. In other circumstances, Company offers services, or sells products jointly with affiliated businesses. You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is connected to such transactions with that affiliated business.

**Agents:**  
We employ other firms and individuals to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, myPhoneShop ‘s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

**Employees:**  
We limit the access to your Personal Information to those personnel who need to know that information to provide products or services to you.

**Business Transfers:**  
In certain cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these manners of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Furthermore, if myPhoneShop, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that the Company goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such handovers may occur, and that any acquirer of the Company may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

**Protection of Company and Others:**  
We may issue Personal Information when we are certain that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of myPhoneShop, our employees, users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Security of Personal Information:  
**Your myPhoneShop account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by choosing and protecting your password suitably and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you are done accessing your account.  
myPhoneShop ‘s order form asks users to enter Personal Information such as a credit card number, that information is encrypted with industry-standard Secure Socket Layers (“SSL”) encryption to keep your online order secure. When the letters “http” in the URL address change to “https”, the “s” specifies you are in a secure area employing SSL. myPhoneShop maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with guidelines to protect your Personal Information. myPhoneShop endeavors to protect user data to ensure that user account information is kept private; however, the Company cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user data and other information at any time.

The Website may include links to other sites. myPhoneShop is not accountable for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs data collected on the Website.

**What personal information can I access?**  
myPhoneShop permits access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain circumstances, updating that data. This list may change as our Website grows and additional information may be needed.

  * Name
  * Date of Birth
  * Gender
  * Delivery Address
  * Mobile Number
  * Telephone Number
  * E-mail Address

**What choices do I have?  
**

  * As stated, you can always choose not to disclose information to use, though it may be required to take advantage of certain Company features, including the ability to purchase items through the Website.
  * The ability to add or update certain data, such as those listed in the “What Personal Information Can I Access” section above. When updating information, we may maintain a copy of the information you provided before the revision in our private records.
  * If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, including promotional offers, please specify this preference by changing your account settings, or by informing us by using the “Unsubscribe” feature in any email we send. Note that if you do not want to receive legal notices, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of myPhoneShop’s Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
myPhoneShop amends to this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of data we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will let you know by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

**Questions or concerns**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: customerservice@myPhoneShop.com.ph
